fullcircle.com 2018-12-22

# Full Circle - Privacy Policy

## Modified & Effective May 31, 2017

Welcome to our Website; thank you for visiting! Full Circle ("Company") is committed to protecting the privacy of our customers and makes this policy easily available throughout our Website to assist you in understanding the handling of information in the course of using the Website.

This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and is subject to the Company Terms of Use. Your use of the Website and any personal information you provide on the Website remains subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy and our Service Policy. 

### Information Company Collects

If you sign up or inquire about service, the Company collects a variety of information, such as your name and address, email address, payment information, account preferences and other information that is personal in nature.

The Company does not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages, except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt in or opt out. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications by emailing us as at [policies@fullcircle.com](mailto:policies@fullcircle.com) or by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link in emails sent by the Company or by replying to any email sent by the Company and entering the word UNSUBSCRIBE in the subject line. The Company may, however use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major Website changes or for customer service purposes).

If you submit personally identifiable information to the Company through the Website, the Company may use your personal information to operate, maintain and provide to you the features and functionality of the Website.

The Company uses both your personally identifiable information and certain non-personally identifiable information (such as anonymous user usage data, cookies, IP addresses, browser type, clickstream data, etc.) to improve the quality and design of the Website and to create new features, promotions, functionality and services by storing, tracking and analyzing user preferences and trends.

When you visit the Website, the Company may use cookies – a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters that uniquely identifies your browser – sent to your computer for reference purposes to enhance visitor experience and provide faster access to Website features. The Company uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. A session cookie can make it easier for you to navigate our site and is temporary, disappearing after you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Website. Persistent cookies can perform such activities as storing your password and can be removed by following your web browser help file directions. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the Website may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled.

If you post comments or articles to any forum, blog or message board on this Website, any personally identifiable information you provide in those comments or articles may be read, collated and used by anyone viewing them. As such, the Company is not responsible for personally identifiable information you may choose to make available through these channels.

### When Company Discloses Information

The Company does not share your personally identifiable information (such as name or email address) with other third-party companies for their commercial or marketing use.

The Company provides personally identifiable information and non-personally identifiable information to affiliated companies or other businesses or persons for the purpose of processing such information on our behalf. The Company requires that these parties agree to process such information in compliance with the Company’s Privacy Policy, and the Company uses reasonable efforts to limit their use of such information and to use other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

The Company does share non-personally identifiable information (such as anonymous user usage data, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.) with interested third-parties to assist them in understanding the usage patterns for certain content, services, advertisements, promotions and/or functionality on the Website.

The Company may release personally identifiable information and/or non-personally identifiable information if required to do so by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with state and federal laws (such as U.S. Copyright Law) or respond to a court order, subpoena or search warrant.

The Company also reserves the right to disclose personally identifiable information and/or non-personally identifiable information that the Company believes, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to enforce our Terms of Use, take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend itself against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist government enforcement agencies, to protect the security or integrity of its Website and to protect the rights, property or personal safety of the Company, our users or others.

### YOUR CHOICES

You may, of course, decline to submit personally identifiable information through the Website, in which case, the Company may not be able to provide certain services to you. You may update or correct your personal information and email preferences at any time by visiting your Account Profile page.

To protect your privacy and security, the Company takes reasonable steps (such as requesting a unique password) to verify your identity before granting you profile access or making corrections. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information at all times.

### SECURITY

The Company uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. The Company cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to the Company, and you do so at your own risk.

If the Company learns of a security systems breach, then it may attempt to notify you so that you can take appropriate protective steps. The Company may post a notice on the Website if a security breach occurs. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive a free, written notice of a security breach (or to withdraw your consent from receiving electronic notice), you should notify the Company.

You may submit any questions you may have about our security procedures by emailing us at [policies@fullcircle.com](mailto:policies@fullcircle.com).

### LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES

This Website may contain links to other sites that are not controlled in any way by the Company. Please be aware of this when you click on any such links; the Company is not responsible for the privacy practices and/or policies of any website other than our own.

### OUR COMMITMENT TO CHILDRENS' PRIVACY

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, the Company does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information or non-personally identifiable information on the Website from persons under 13 years of age, and no part of our Website is directed to persons under 13. If you are under 13 years of age, then please do not use or access the Website at any time or in any manner. If the Company learns that personally identifiable information of persons under 13 years of age has been collected on the Website without verified parental consent, then the Company will take the appropriate steps to delete this information.

### CONTACT DETAILS

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, or you wish to contact the Company by phone, email or postal mail, its contact information is as follows:

1-866-206-8080  
800 Maynard Ave S #403, Seattle, WA 98134 

### DISCLOSURE AND UPDATES

This Privacy Policy may be revised periodically, and this will be reflected by the “effective date” above. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. In general, the Company only uses your personal information in the manner described in the Privacy Policy in effect when the Company received the personal information you provided. Your continued use of the Website constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any future revisions.

For revisions to this Privacy Policy that may be materially less restrictive on the Company's use or disclosure of the personal information you have already provided, the Company will attempt to obtain your consent before implementing such revisions with respect to such information.

Copyright © 2017 Full Circle. All rights reserved.
